

# NATHAN GOH JUN HAO

Open for challenges and opportunities while being careful and systematic. Experienced in a goal & teamwork oriented environment to carry out daily task effectively. Currently in look for exciting global industrial change for new challenges.

#### **Contact Details**

+60 16-2398645

gohjunhao95@gmail.com

86, Jalan Duyung 4, Taman Duyung, 70200, Seremban, Negeri Sembilan, Malaysia

## **EXPERIENCE**



June 2022 - Current	Kibing Group Malaysia Sdn Bhd	<b>Process Coordinator</b>
---------------------	-------------------------------	----------------------------

- In charge of coordinating communications between departments & HQ to smooth daily processes
- Assist to interpret messages/execution order given by HQ
- Responsible of departmental administration work
- Personal assistant of Technical Director

#### May 2021 - June 2022 Daikin Malaysia Sales & Services **Service Provider Support Executive**

- In charge of recruitment & developments of Service Provider for HQ & State branches
- Coordinating for Service Providers training & onboarding between HQ & States branches to achieve service launching target
- Provide assistance to Service Providers during, before & after job service
- Attend customer pre-service enquiries & post-service complaints
- In charge of E-Commerce platform (Lazada, Shopee) customer chat & assisting to manage SKUs stock count

#### Globee Services Sdn Bhd **Customer Experience Representative** Feb 2021 - Apr 2021 Attending to merchants, riders and customers enquiries & complaints through Emails, Chats & Calls Nov 2018 – Jul 2020 Sales Support & Marketing Executive **Matrix Concepts Sdn Bhd**

- Creating marketing campaigns to attract buyers and expedite sales
- Organising annual events at club house or project site to drive crowds and walk-in buyers
- Ensuring marketing collaterals are sufficient to reach different target market
- Arranging property exhibitions & roadshows, making sure booth set-ups, scale models & brochures are in order
- Updating buyers loan ageing report & working with sales team to maintain a robust transaction record
- Updating sales team on cancellation units to quickly replace with new buyers within the shortest time
- Compiling & reporting daily sales record by end of the day

Dec 2017 – Feb 2018	Story World Sdn Bhd	Internship
Assisting in administration works, compiling data & market research		
Apr 2017	Troopers Malaysia	Ground Team Supervisor
Supervise and leading teams of freelance brand ambassador for Uber		

Achieving daily targets by assisting new users to sign up for promotion

### **EDUCATION**



2016 – 2018	<b>Bachelor of Business and Commerce</b>	Victoria University, Sunway Campus
<ul> <li>Major in Mark</li> </ul>	seting (GPA 4.789)	
2015	Bachelor of Business and Commerce	Monash University, Sunway Campus
<ul> <li>Major in Mark</li> </ul>	xeting & Finance	
2013 – 2014	Monash University Foundation Year (MUFY)	Sunway College University
• MUFY Score 67.88 / 100		
2008 – 2012	SPM	SMJK Chan Wa (Cawangan)

Application Skills	3	Language Skil	Is
Microsoft Office		English	
JavaScript		Chinese	
Teamwork		Malay	
Flexibility		Cantonese	

# EXTRA CURRICULAR



2020	Mount. Kota Kinabalu Hiking Completion
2019	Global Leadership Summit @ Agape Community Church – AV Crew
2017	Global Leadership Summit @ Agape Community Church – AV Crew
2015	Viper Challenge
2014	National Scouts Guides Skills Tournament @ SMJK Chan Wa - Photographer
2013	Rover Scout of SMJK Chan Wa
	Program Latihan Khidmat Negara (PLKN)
2012	Scout Troop of SMJK Chan Wa – Publicity
	Maths & Science Society – Assistant Secretary
2009 – 2012	National Scouts Guides Skills Tournament

## **PROJECTS**



2018	Hope: Christmas Musical by Agape Community Church – AV Crew

In charge of creating & programming lights effect to enhance overall experience

### 2015 Mobile App Development

- Project based assignment to create a business idea
- Conducting market feasibility & testing
- Pitching the business idea to company representatives